export default [
    {
        question: "monday",
        answer: "lundi"
    },
    {
        question: "tuesday",
        answer: "mardi",
        highlight: "I talks",
    },
    {
        question: "wednesday",
        answer: "mercredi",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "thursday",
        answer: "jeudi",
        highlight: "She talks",
    },
    {
        question: "friday",
        answer: "vendredi",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "saturday",
        answer: "samedi",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "sunday",
        answer: "dimanche",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "january",
        answer: "janvier",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "feburary",
        answer: "février",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "march",
        answer: "mars",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "april",
        answer: "avril",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "may",
        answer: "mai",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "june",
        answer: "juin",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "july",
        answer: "juillet",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "august",
        answer: "août",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "september",
        answer: "septembre",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "october",
        answer: "octobre",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "november",
        answer: "novembre",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "december",
        answer: "décembre",
        highlight: "You talks",
    }
]